{
    "Items": [
        {
            "question": "Which vocabulary represent to 烏賊?",
            "chinese": "烏賊",
			"correctAns": "cuttlefish",
			"wrongAns": ["tuna", "octopus","gecko"]
        },
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 蜥蜴?",
			"chinese": "蜥蜴",
			"correctAns": "lizard",
			"wrongAns": ["gecko", "chameleon", "cuttlefish"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 三文魚?",
			"chinese": "三文魚",
			"correctAns": "salmon",
			"wrongAns": ["toad", "cobra", "snake"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 金魚?",
			"chinese": "金魚",
			"correctAns": "goldfish",
			"wrongAns": ["goldenfish", "oyster", "jerryfish" ]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 蜈蚣?",
			"chinese": "蜈蚣",
			"correctAns": "centipede",
			"wrongAns": ["cockroach", "ant", "ng gon", "Cub"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 蒼蠅?",
			"chinese": "蒼蠅",
			"correctAns": "fly",
			"wrongAns": ["fries", "bee", "fai", "pullet"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 蚊子?",
			"chinese": "蚊子",
			"correctAns": "mosquito",
			"wrongAns": ["fly", "duck", "butterfly", "flamingo"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 青蛙?",
			"chinese": "青蛙",
			"correctAns": "frog",
			"wrongAns": ["kit", "cub", "pup", "fingerling"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 毛毛蟲?",
			"chinese": "毛毛蟲",
			"correctAns": "caterpillar",
			"wrongAns": ["warm", "scallop", "fledgling", "peachick"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 螃蟹?",
			"chinese": "螃蟹",
			"correctAns": "crab",
			"wrongAns": ["shrimp", "kitten", "pinkie", "rabbit"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 蟾蜍?",
			"chinese": "蟾蜍",
			"correctAns": "toad",
			"wrongAns": ["spiderling", "cosset", "tadpole", "poult"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 臭鼬?",
			"chinese": "臭鼬",
			"correctAns": "skunk",
			"wrongAns": ["gibbon", "calf", "pup", "hatchling"]
		}
    ]
}